adremover.org 2017-09-19

# Ad Remover | Get Ad Remover Today

_Effective Date: 12/01/15_

Browsetech LLC (DBA “Ad Remover”) privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers the collection and use of personal information (“Personal Information”) that we may gather any time you interact with us, such as when you visit adremover.org, purchase, download, or use Ad Remover products, or when you contact our customer support or sales departments (collectively referred to as the “Web site”). This policy describes our data privacy practices, including what type of information is gathered, how Ad Remover uses the information, and how we safeguard your Personal Information when you submit it to us at www.adremover.org. At Ad Remover, protecting your privacy is important to us. You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. Personal Information may be processed by Ad Remover in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent.

If you have questions or complaints regarding Ad Remover, please contact us at 3267 Bee Caves Rd, Suite 107-165, Austin, Texas 78746 USA or by clicking here . 

Why Ad Remover Collects Personal Information  
Ad Remover collects your Personal Information to provide you the best services and products available. By collecting certain Personal Information, we can present our Web site and its contents to you, including any interactive features, give you the information and services that you request from us, and offer you certain rewards and features related to the Web site and programs. For example, we use Personal Information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. By maintaining an accurate customer database, we are able to send notifications via e-mail to keep you informed about the status of your orders or accounts, to provide updates and technical notices, and to keep records of our transactions. These messages are essential to the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our products and services.   
Ad Remover collects websites you have visited in order to improve our ad blocking abilities and speed, information about any websites you visit is collected in aggregate and cannot be associated to you personally. We retain this information in order to continuously improve our business, services, and ad blocking intelligence based on aggregating and normalizing the data collected across all systems.   
Ad Remover also respects our contracts with you and other parties and legal processes. As a result, Ad Remover may collect information to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, or to otherwise protect our rights or those of third parties, and to comply with applicable laws, regulations, and legal process;   
Finally, Ad Remover collects information to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it and as otherwise necessary or useful for us to conduct our business, so long as such use is permitted by law. For example, if you request a newsletter, we will collect information sufficient to provide you with such newsletter. 

What Information We Collect

Personal Information Ad Remover collects your Personal Information at a variety of points, including when you place an order, (which may require you to provide personal information, including a credit card number, to our commerce providers) register software, request services or take part in other activities on our Web site. For example, we often ask for your Personal Information when you are conferring with one of our customer support technicians, downloading a new product or program update, registering your software or purchasing a product. During these interactions we will collect Personal Information relevant to your transacting with Ad Remover, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, shipping address and credit card information along with information about the Ad Remover products you own, such as the activation code or key code, date of purchase and information relating to a support issue. Please be aware that if you prefer not to provide us with your Personal Information, because such information may be necessary for us to provide certain services, we may not be able to, or may choose not to, make such services available to you. 

Regarding Children Ad Remover does not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13. If you believe that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 through this website, please contact us. 

Cookies and Other Technologies Following common e-commerce practices, Ad Remover uses “cookies” and other technologies to collect non-personal data that enables us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of Ad Remover’s Website, and for reporting purposes to track sales. See our Cookie Policy for additional information. 

Additionally, Ad Remover gathers general information about visits to our Website and stores this information in log files. This information is stored in anonymous profiles and is not associated with a user’s account. This information includes the number of total visits to our Web site, search terms and which browser is used to view our Web site (including the version number). No Personal Information is contained in this data. 

On occasion, Ad Remover also gathers general information about click-through usage of key features within our software to confirm that software updates are providing the intended user experience. This information is collected in aggregate form and stored in a manner that cannot be associated with any individual. The information includes total clicks on select features available in our software and is used to understand how our software is used, enabling us to improve the software, and provide the best possible user experience for our customers. 

If you opt in to a program to automatically submit feedback to improve the user experience, we may collect additional information obtained automatically upon use of the Ad Remover program. The ways in which we may store and use the information will be provided to you when you opt in to the program. 

We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. 

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings. We do not respond to a browsers do not track signal. Because non-personal information does not identify who you are, we do not limit the ways we may use or share non-personal information. For example, we may share non-personal information with our affiliates, suppliers, employees and agents, other businesses, and the government. 

Sharing Your Personal Information Ad Remover is committed to protecting your privacy. Ad Remover will not, under any circumstances, share, rent or sell your Personal Information in ways other than as outlined in this privacy policy nor does Ad Remover trade or exchange mailing lists with organizations other than affiliates or contractors that assist us in providing services and the Web site. Ad Remover shares and gives access to personal information to our employees and agents (including employees and agents of our affiliates) in the course of operating our businesses. Ad Remover also shares your Personal Information with our contractors that assist us in our efforts to fulfill our obligations to you. Some contractors include credit card processing companies to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf and a customer support provider to supply live assisted-support. 

Ad Remover maintains this information; but we reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, legal process served on our Website, law, or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting website visitors who violate our rules, or engage in behavior that is harmful to other visitors, or is illegal. 

If all or part of our business is sold, merged, dissolved, acquired, or in a similar transaction, or in the event of a corporate reorganization, the successor company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

How We Communicate with You Ad Remover has an optional e-mail service for customers who wish to periodically receive promotional information, such as general product, service and Ad Remover news. Users can sign up for emails through one of the following processes: (1) an online Purchase; (2) registering through the full application; (3) registering through the trial application; and (4) signing up on the Ad Remover website. Customers are provided the option to opt-out within each e-mail. If you no longer wish to receive Ad Remover communications, you may “unsubscribe” from our mailing program at any time in the following ways:

• By clicking on the auto-unsubscribe link included in each e-mail  
• By contacting our technical support department: CLICK HERE TO CONTACT SUPPORT.  
• By visiting your Account page here and changing your preference on the form. 

We will then update our database and take reasonable measures so that no further promotional correspondence should be sent to the e-mail address. You may, however, still receive transactional messages. 

Transactional Messages Ad Remover sends required notifications via e-mail to keep you informed of the status of your orders or accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. This service is used for messages that are important for the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our services. When you purchase or register a product online, we require an e-mail address for completion of the transaction, which we will use for these communications. In order to stop receiving these notifications, please contact our technical support team by clicking here. You will be opted out of further communications within 10 business days. 

Ways to Update Your Personal Information Ad Remover maintains our customer database in an effort to keep your Personal Information accurate for the purposes for which it is used. It is your right to be able to update your Personal Information as needed. You can correct out-of-date information by logging in and visiting the account settings page. Please contact us at support@adremover.org if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. 

Ad Remover’ Commitment to Data Security The security of your personal information is important to us, and we take reasonable precautions to protect your information. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately. 

Links to other sites Our website and products include links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Ad Remover. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

California Privacy Rights California Civil code § 1798.83 provides certain rights to California residents, including the right to request information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. To request such information, please contact us as described below. 

Acceptance of this Privacy Policy By using the Web site or any services provided through the Web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Privacy Policy Revisions and Notifications We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, and by means of a prominent notice on our home page. 

AdStopper.com Contact Information For questions about this policy as well as product-related technical support: click here. 

Send all other correspondence to: 

_Ad Remover_  
_3267 Bee Cave Rd. Suite 107-165  
Austin, Texas 78746 USA  
support@adremover.org_
